tastecard.co.uk 2014-06-27

# Tastecard - The UK's largest diners club - 2 for 1 or 50% off at thousands of restaurants nationwide

Taste Marketing Limited ( **We** ) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This policy (together with our website terms of use and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that we hold about you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 ( **Act** ), the data controller is Taste Marketing Limited of 1 Victoria Court, Bank Square, Morley, Leeds, West Yorkshire, LS27 9SE. 

## INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT FROM YOU

We may collect and process the following data about you:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site www.tastecard.co.uk ( **our site** ).
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
  * We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.
  * Details of your visits to our site and the resources that you access.

## IP ADDRESSES

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, geographic location (if you allow when prompted by your browser), operating system and browser type, for system administration. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

## COOKIES

We may use cookies to help personalise your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard drive by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalise the pages on our site, or register on our site for any services we provide, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. When you return to our site the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the features that you customised.

We may also use cookies to deliver relevant adverts on other reputable websites you visit that show advertising. They will appear in banner format and will be based on your activity whilst browsing our site.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of our site.

Cookie Name | Purpose | Expires  
---|---|---  
sess | The cookie is used to collect information about how you use and personalise our site. | When you close your web browser  
usr | The cookie is used to work out if you are a returning user and associates you with your past activity on our site | 2 years after creation  
  
**Google Analytics:**

__utma

__utmb

__utmc

__utmz

__utmx

| These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve our site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to our site, where visitors have come to our site from and the pages they visited. | To find out more, please view [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) and [Cookies & Google Analytics](http://code.google.com/apis/analytics/docs/concepts/gaConceptsCookies.html)  
  
## WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ( **EEA** ). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

## USES MADE OF THE INFORMATION

We use information held about you in the following ways:

  * To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.
  * To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.
  * To notify you about changes to our service.

We may also use your data, or permit selected third parties, such as participating restaurants or Livebookings Holdings Limited, trading as Bookatable ( **Bookatable** ), to use your data to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we may contact you about these by post or telephone.

We do not sell, rent or lease customer lists to third parties. We may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, we may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to us, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale to you.

If you are a new customer, and where we permit selected third parties, such as participating restaurants or Bookatable, to use your data, we (or they) will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this.

## DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
  * If Taste Marketing Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Taste Marketing Limited, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## YOUR RIGHTS

You have the right to ask us, or our selected third parties, not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We, or such third parties, will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at [enquiries@tastecard.co.uk](mailto:enquiries@tastecard.co.uk).

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

## CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.

## CONTACT

Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should either be emailed to [enquiries@tastecard.co.uk](mailto:enquiries@tastecard.co.uk) or addressed to Taste Marketing Limited, 22 Viaduct Street, Huddersfield, HD1 6AJ.
